msi.eu 2015-06-16

# MSI Europe - Computer, Laptop, Notebook, Desktop, Mainboard, Graphics and more

MSI takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy and how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. MSI reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion.

##  Collection of personal information

MSI collects personal information through various means, such as through Web site cookies, your purchase of MSI products, and your response to MSI surveys.

When you register with MSI as a member or when you register MSI product, during the registration, MSI will ask for your personal information, including but not limited to full name, email address, birthday, gender, postal code, occupation, and interests, in order to provide better customer services. MSI also collects customer's Web browsing activities through Web server log files.

In addition to membership and product registration, MSI may collect personal information you provided in, including but not limited to Events, Promotion, Competition, On-line survey held by MSI or MSI partners.

##  How your personal information is used

To provide better services to our customers is the primary goal of MSI when collecting personal information.

MSI processes and researches collected personal information from various sources in order to get closer to customer needs and interests.

Unless you actively choose not to receive information from MSI, we will send you information periodically, such as product release, membership benefits, and MSI Newsletter.

##  Protection of your personal information

MSI does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested

MSI may share your information with MSI partners and we may send you information about MSI partners' products or services which may interest you.

If you do not want to receive promotional materials regarding MSI partners' products or services, and you indicate this preference when you provide your personal information to MSI, MSI will honor your preference by not providing your information to MSI partners.

##  Use of cookies

In order to improve our site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A "cookie" is a small piece of information which a web server can store temporarily with your web browser. This is useful for having your browser remember some specific information which the web server can later retrieve.

In general, MSI uses cookies to:

  1. Identify web user. A cookie will be created when you login at our web page and will be destroyed when you logout.
  2. Estimate visit count. Every client browser will be assigned a unique cookie which will then be used to calculate the behavior difference between registered customers and normal visitors.
  3. Track browsing pattern. MSI analyzes browsing patterns through cookies.
  4. Measure web traffic. MSI utilizes cookies to understand the size of audience and traffic patterns within the site.

##  Announcements & Changes

MSI reserves the right to update or change this Policy at any time. MSI will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to your email address recorded in our customer database or by placing a prominent notice on our web site.

When you are browsing MSI Web site or using our services, please also check our private policy regarding to that specific service. MSI welcomes all kinds of suggestions; please feel fee to contact us if you have any question.
